听好了
Listen up.
麦克斯与卡洛琳在参加一个盛大的好莱坞首映
Max and Caroline are at a big Hollywood premiere.
她们说哈里森·福特也在
They say Harrison Ford is there.
告诉韩·索罗"憨[韩]跟他问好"
Tell Han Solo, "Hello from Han."
永远自撸的"汉"
Who always does it solo.
这里全都是名人
Yeah, this place is crawling with celebs.
大伙都在呢
Everyone's here.
马特·戴蒙 凯特·布兰切特 艾米·舒默的妹妹
Matt Damon, Cate Blanchett, Amy Schumer's sister.
如果见到毕·雷诺斯 跟他说他皮带在我这
If you see Burt Reynolds, tell him I have his belt.
拍几张奶照
Snap some boob pics.
拍些一线的D奶 或者二线的C奶
Some A-list D's or some B-list C's.
没办法 我的手机没电了
I can't. My phone's dead.
但你现在就在用它打电话啊
But you're on your phone.
这里一团乱呢
Big ruckus here.
马特·戴蒙刚往唐·钱德尔身上丢了千层饼
Matt Damon just threw a puff pastry at Don Cheadle.
我们视频通话如何
How bout we FaceTime?
没办法 没信号
Can't. No reception.
但我们不是还说着电话吗
But we're talking to you right now.
我得走了
Well, I gotta go.
茱莉亚·罗伯茨想共乘一台便宜出租车
Julia Roberts wants to split an UberX.
骗阿憨好过意不去
I feel bad lying to Han.
他今年已经被网上用假身份的人骗三次了
I mean, he's already been catfished three times this year.
不怪他 其中两次是我
To be fair, two of those times were me.
我们也不算骗人啊
And we're not really lying.
如果我们想 也是能去好莱坞派对的啊
We could have gone to that Hollywood party if we wanted to.
前提是被邀请了
And had been invited.
而且还没被保安给踢出来的话
And hadn't been kicked out by security.
电话还没挂断呢
We're still on the line.
我们不能回去那里了
We can never go back there.
你的新男人真好
So nice of your new man
送我们冷压果汁篮
to send us a pressed juice basket.
好洛城风啊
So LA.
好难喝啊
So gross!
我爱死它们了 它们够恶心
I love them. They're disgusting.
这瓶感觉像舔甜菜根的起落架
This one's like licking a beet's undercarriage.
但兰迪的心意还是很感人
Still, it was really thoughtful of Randy.
他一定很喜欢你
He must really like you,
也很希望你能保持标准身材
and really want you to stay regular.
是啊 走了那么多弯路
Yeah, someone really buried the lead
终于走上了被人好好对待的康庄大道了
on this whole being treated well thing,
我已经想他了
and I miss him.
你们30分钟前才见
You saw him 30 minutes ago.
感觉像35分钟了
Feels like 35.
这是怎么回事 我得性病了吗
What is that about? Do I have shingles?
天啊 我刚收到一封电邮
Oh, my God. I just got an e-mail.
全球最炙手可热的女演员正在来的路上
The world's most in-demand actress is on her way over
要来谈在我人生的电影中出演我
to talk about playing me in the movie of my life.
贝蒂·怀特要来啦
Betty White's coming here?
是詹妮弗·劳伦斯
It's Jennifer Lawrence!
艾米·舒默的妹妹的死党
Amy Schumer's sister's best friend.
制片方他们刚安排好
The studio just set it up.
她想见我看看喜不喜欢我的范儿
She wants to meet me to see if she digs my vibe.
我也希望我的电动范儿[棒]在
Oh, wish I had my vibe.
他们不让我把它带上飞机
They wouldn't let me bring it on the plane.
我能拿它做啥坏事啊
What was I gonna do?
用高潮恐吓飞机上的人吗
Terrorize everyone with pleasure?
我最好去刷个牙
Oh, I better go brush my teeth.
我可不想詹妮弗·劳伦斯觉得
I don't want Jennifer Lawrence to think
我舔了哈密瓜的腋下
I licked a cantaloupe's armpit.
《饥饿游戏》的女主角要来这里吗
The star of "The Hunger Games" is coming here?
我跟她会有很多共同点
We will have lots in common.
比如 我也为了食物杀过小孩
I mean, I've killed kids for food.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
有人知道怎么关掉电梯里的火灾警报器吗
Does anyone know how to shut off the fire alarm in the elevator?
这个鼠尾草烧得可旺了
'Cause this sage is really popping off.
有麻烟要分享啊
Hey, puff puff pass.
这个不是拿来抽的
Ah, you don't smoke it.
这是拿来净化你的灵气 或其他鬼东西的
No, it cleans your aura or some crap like that.
感觉好精神化啊
Well, that sounds spiritual.
我的治疗师说
Oh, you know, my healer says
我至今还没怀孕的原因是因为
the reason that I haven't been able to get pregnant
我的灵气
is that my aura is filthier
比我妇产科医生的图片分享网还肮脏
than my gynecologist's Instagram.
但他发的我那张 很多人点赞啊
But I did get a lot of likes.
苏菲
Ugh, Sophie,
我闻到了二手嬉皮烟
I'm getting second hand hippie.
苏菲 我得把这玩意弄出去
Sophie, I have got to get this out of here
不然詹妮弗·劳伦斯会以为这是我的范儿
or Jennifer Lawrence will think this is my vibe.
我想走优雅脱俗 而不是逗比男星路线
I'm going for Grace Kelly not Woody Harrelson.
你这是犯了大错
Well, that's a mistake.
你知道吗
You know what?
我的治疗师 奥德拉 给了我一堆任务
My healer, Audra, gave me a whole list of things
我想怀孕必须得照做
that I need to do in order to get pregnant.
其中一条是"从正面上前洞洞吗"
Is one of them, "Have sex the front way"?
还有"吃苹果 冥想
Yeah, also, "Eat apples, meditate,
雪茄减量"
cut down on cigars."
她还说我要练习
She also said that I have to practice
对大家有爱包容
loving kindness with everyone.
对那些惹我不快的人也要如此
Even the people who trigger my negativity.
不过呢
Yeah, but you know what?
我这个人甜得就像那
I'm as sweet as the sugar substitute
给了我半个家族癌症的代糖
that gave half my family cancer, yeah.
其实你不是永远都
You're maybe not always
对别人如那代糖一般甜
sweet as sugar substitute to everyone.
我没有吗
I'm not?
这傻逼又来了
Well, here comes this idiot.
这样吧
You know what?
我会对你加倍好 这样我才能怀宝宝
I'm gonna be real nice to you so that I can have a baby.
所以我不再也不管你的傻逼嘴里
So I don't care what kind of crap comes out
又冒出什么二逼话
of your stupid pie hole.
天啊 我简直坏死了
Oh, my God, I'm a monster.
天啊 你觉得会是詹妮弗·劳伦斯吗
Oh, my God, do you think that's Jennifer Lawrence?
真有效率 好有明星风范
That was fast. What a star.
准时而且上门还比叫鸭便宜
Prompt and she costs less than a man.
也可能是兰迪 我跟他分开足足38分钟了
Or maybe it's Randy. It's been a whole 38 minutes.
这都让我"性"致盎然了
Aww, that's making me horny.
可惜这不在我的任务名单上
Yeah, and that's not on my list.
我过来是告诉你今晚我不能过夜了
I came over to tell you I can't stay the night tonight.
我得去一趟迈阿密
I gotta go to Miami.
我的委托人在大闹约翰尼·德普的新片
My client's causing trouble on the new Johnny Depp movie.
我的委托人就是约翰尼·德普
My client's Johnny Depp.
又是另一部"海盗"电影吗
Is it another "pirates" movie?
因为他上次那集我"才看"了四小时呢
'Cause I'm only four hours into the last one.
卡洛琳·钱宁的办公室
Caroline Channing's office.
我是她的助理泰伊莎 请稍等
This is her assistant Tiesha. Please hold.
给了我自己一个助理 因为我值得拥有
I gave myself an assistant 'cause I deserve one.
看 就是这样
Oh, yeah, there it is.
天啊 我又要被惹毛了
Oh, my God, I'm getting triggered.
糟糕
Oh, man.
我的狗保姆刚辞职了
My dog sitter just quit.
她嫁给埃迪·墨菲了
She married Eddie Murphy.
现在没人帮我照顾布鲁诺了
Now I don't have anybody to watch Bruno.
我能帮你照顾他啊
Oh, I can watch Bruno.
那你想去我家跟他待着吗
Would you want to stay with him at my place?
到你在富人区的那间
At your beautiful house in the hills
能看见好莱坞地标的漂亮房子里吗
with an amazing view of the Hollywood sign?
行吧 是看在我超超想去的份上
Ugh, fine, but only 'cause I really want to.
真不巧 大表姐被狗仔包
Okay, so unfortch J Law got swarmed by the paps
只能改时间了啦
so she has to resche.
天啊
Oh, boy.
我真是选错时间戒雪茄了
I picked the wrong week to quit smoking cigars.
兰迪 这风景真是太赞了
Randy, that view is so amazing.
这里近到"好莱坞"三个大字只看得到"好"了
We're so close I can see the "Ho" Of the Hollywood sign.
我敢打赌上面是写着
And I bet it's saying,
我能看到威廉斯堡的"好"骚货
"I can see the ho of Williamsburg."
这地方真是太美了
Wow, this place is gorgeous.
麦克斯上一个约会的男的 床垫都是在地上
The last guy Max dated had a mattress on the floor
还有个叫谢拉的女人住在地窖
and a lady named Sheila living in the crawl space.
卡洛琳 你是想让我嫉妒她前男友吗
Caroline, are you trying to make me jealous?
你没啥好担心的
Oh, you have nothing to worry about.
那男的绝对不可能还活着
There's no way that guy's still alive.
接下来的24小时
Look, the next 24 hours,
就把这里当做自己家
just treat this place like it's yours.
放心 我会好好照顾布鲁诺
Don't worry, I will take really good care of Bruno.
我会让他睡在我的双峰之间
I'll let him sleep right in the hills.
上次这么嫉妒我的狗时
I haven't been this jealous of my dog
是我看到他每天都能给自己舔蛋蛋
since I saw him licking his own balls every day.
兰迪 这里够私密清幽吗
Randy, would you say it's private up here?
够私密到足以跟明星开会
Like private enough to have a meeting with a celebrity
一位我不会说出名字
who I'm not at will to name,
但是是詹妮弗·劳伦斯
but it's Jennifer Lawrence.
这里很清幽
Yeah, it's really quiet up here.
也就坡上有个邻居
Just one neighbor up the hill.
一个老家伙 穿脏兮兮的运动服有型到炸
Old guy. Rocks the hell out of a stained sweat suit.
我们处得挺好
We get along great.
我们从没说过话
We've never spoken.
我收不到信号 你的无线网密码是什么
I can't get a signal. What's your Wi-Fi password?
1, 2, 5, lowercase B,
大写D 破折号 破折号 6 3
uppercase D, dash, dash, 6, 3,
小写f 大写F 5 2 1
lowercase F, uppercase F, 5, 2, 1.
或者你去外面就能收到信号
Or you can get some reception outside.
好了 我得走了
All right, I gotta go.
过来 乖狗狗
Come here, big boy.
谁是爸爸的乖狗狗 乖
Who's Daddy's big boy? Yes.
这招对我也管用喔
That call works on me too, FYI.
过来 乖狗狗
Come here, big boy.
卡洛琳 哪里信号最好
Caroline, where's the best reception?
坡下 靠近篱笆
Down this hill behind the hedge...
那是蛇吗
Oh, is that a snake?
在这张桌上我也收到了点信号
Ooh, getting some bars on this table.
我要打给餐厅
I'm gonna call the diner.
麦克斯 我的乖闺女
Hey, Max, how's my girl?
你有钱 出名 开始开混合动力车了吗
Are you rich, famous, and driving a Prius yet?
厄尔 你绝对想不到我们现在在哪
Earl, you would not believe where we are.
我正俯视着整个洛城
I am looking down on all of LA.
我在这也是"俯视"整个洛城
Oh, I'm doing that from here.
问问麦克斯有没有跟苏菲联系
Ask Max if she talked to Sophie.
我今早没有收到她发给我裙内风光照
I didn't get an up the skirt selfie this morning
我开始担心她了
and I'm worried.
我意外收到了那图
I got it by accident.
而我也希望谈论这事
And I'm hoping talking about it
能让我从这梦魇中解脱
will somehow free me from it.
能转发给我吗
Can you forward it to me?
我的手机直接送你吧
You know what? Just take my phone.
我去买个新的
I'll buy a new one.
别 吹了
Stop...blowing.
Stop blowing.
吹...
Blowing...
谢谢
Thank you!
您会怎么给洛城的"吹"活儿
So how would you rate the LA blow job
跟纽约的"吹活儿"[口交]打分呢
compared to the ones in New York?
这个不用我出嘴出力
This one was less work.
当詹妮弗·劳伦斯来这里面试我时
When Jennifer Lawrence gets here to interview me,
其实我也算是在面试她
just know, I'm also kind of interviewing her.
我知道她跟我们颜值相近
I mean, I know she has my looks,
但她能像我这么天真单纯吗
but does she have my naivete?
那个法语的意思是"小平胸"吗
Is that French for "small boobs"?
麦克斯 这话我曾在机场的快餐店说过
Max, I know I said this at the airport Arby's,
但我真的能预见你住在这里的画面
but I could totally see you living here.
多谢 妹子
Thanks, girl.
我也能预见你来拜访我们的画面
I could totally see you visiting us.
瞧瞧这台来自未来的电视
And look at this TV from the future.
一根多余的电线都没有
Where are the cords?
看这个 电视机
And watch this. Television...
给我搜塞缪尔·杰克逊
give me Samuel L. Jackson.
正在寻找塞缪尔·杰克逊
Finding Samuel L. Jackson.
哇 他演的电影真多
Wow, he's in every movie.
他就像黑人版的凯文·贝肯
He's like the black Kevin Bacon.
伙计 你能想象我的人生吗
Dude, can you believe my life?
你也看见外面的泳池了
And you saw that pool out there.
不用帮人吹箫也能进去游泳
You don't even have to blow it up.
我们再出去看看吧
Let's go look at it again.
安东尼奥 你能给仙人掌浇浇水吗
Excuse me, Antonio? Could you water that cactus?
它看起来有点干
It's looking a little dry.
那样对佣人说话不会很无礼吧
That didn't sound rude to the help, did it?
我可不想成为那种人
I don't want to be that person.
就是你这种
Meaning you.
好了 詹妮弗·劳伦斯随时会来
Okay, Jennifer Lawrence will be here any minute,
麦克斯 我不得不说
and, Max, I have to say,
今天是我史上头发最漂漂的一天
I'm having the best hair day ever.
今天曾是我史上头发最漂漂的一天
I was having the best hair day ever.
詹妮弗·劳伦斯居然坐直升飞机来这里
Dude, Jennifer Lawrence took a helicopter here.
真是好会摆谱啊
That is so baller.
不 那可能是跟她的狗仔队
No, it's probably the paparazzi following her.
放过我们吧 我们只想讨生活
Leave us be! We're just trying to live!
我们是警察
This is the police!
这一区有一个危险的罪犯
There is a dangerous criminal in the area.
我们在追捕沃尔特·加里·万斯
We are hunting for Walter·Gary·Vance.
大家快进屋
Everyone, go inside.
整片区域已经被封锁
This entire area is on lockdown.
任何人不许越过路障
No one will be allowed to pass the roadblock.
你在干嘛
What're you doing?
有一个连环杀手在逃
Uh, there's a serial killer on the loose.
我在做每一位英雄都会做的事
I'm doing what all heroes do.
我要上推特当键盘侠啊
I'm going on Twitter to add to the chatter.
我要跑去我那颗仙人掌那 给大表姐的人打电话
Okay, I'm running to my cactus to call J Law's people
确保她不会过来这边
and make sure she doesn't come out here.
站住
Stop!
别去那里
Don't go out there.
推特上说
According to Twitter,
那凶手会吃人肉
the murder is a cannibal,
推特上还说
and also according to Twitter,
科勒·卡戴珊在燃烧脂肪
Khloe Kardashian is feeling the burn.
我的老天 吃人肉啊
Oh, my God, a cannibal?
我们必须得进去
We have to get inside.
我有种不祥的预感 我很美味
I have this terrible feeling I'm delicious.
我们进来了
So, here we are.
里面很"安全"
Safe inside
房子是玻璃做的
in a house made of glass
我们踩着高跟鞋
on stilts
走在一个早该地震的城市
in a city long overdue for an earthquake.
我们还以为你是疯狂杀人犯呢
We thought you were a crazy murderer.
我不疯狂 但我现在能
I'm not crazy, but I could just
"杀"掉一盘奶酪
murder a cheese plate right now.
这山上真是太私密了
The hills are so exclusive.
整片区域都被封锁了
I mean, it's all blocked off.
我好久没跨过这么多路障了
I haven't jumped this many hurdles
上一次还是84年的奥运会
since the '84 Olympics.
苏菲 你来干嘛
Sophie, what're you doing here?
詹妮弗·劳伦斯的人在找你
Jennifer Lawrence's people were trying to reach you,
于是他们给酒店打电话
so they called the hotel,
为了向你表示爱意与善意
and to show you some love and kindness,
我大老远跑来告诉你
I came all the way here to tell you.
没错 你觉得这能让我怀上孩子吗
Yeah. Do you think that will get me a baby?
不确定 但你花80块就能在暗网上搞个孩子
Not sure, but you can get a baby for 80 bucks on the dark web.
而且还附送两套衣服哦
And it comes with two outfits.
詹妮弗的人说了什么
What did Jennifer's people say?
我不知道
I don't know.
所以你跑过来告诉我 他们打电话找我
So, you just came up here to tell me that they called,
但你却没有听他们说了什么
but you didn't, like, listen to the words?
你这人就是永远不知足 对吗
Oh, it's never enough for you, is it?
我厌倦了冥想
Ohm getting tired of meditating,
但我觉得起作用了
but I think it's working.
詹妮弗·劳伦斯估计急死了吧
Jennifer Lawrence is probably freaking out
到处都找不到我
that she can't get to me.
世界又不是光绕着你一个人转 贱人
The world doesn't revolve around you, bitch.
我不能再在这里干站着了
I can't just stand here anymore.
我要出去接收手机信号
I'm going outside to get a signal.
你知道你还会在外面"接受"什么事情吗
You know what else you can get outside?
脸被吃掉
Ya face eaten.
我要冒险用我自己的生命
Well, I'm gonna go risk the life I have
换来我想要的生活
to go get the life I want.
听起来像是连姆·尼森的电影
Sounds like a trailer for a Liam Neeson movie.
正在寻找连姆·尼森
Finding Liam Neeson.
祝你好运
Good luck.
那家伙肉身被人劫持的次数 比我的处女身还多
That guy's been taken more times than my virginities.
好了 我收到信号了
All right, I got a signal
还收到一只土狼的警告嚎叫
and a warning growl from a coyote,
但我跟詹妮弗·劳伦斯的人谈过了
but I talked to Jennifer Lawrence's people,
我和她20分钟后会进行视频通话
and she and I are gonna FaceTime in 20 minutes.
如果你的脸还没被吃掉的话
If you still have a face.
布鲁诺去哪儿了
Where's Bruno?
可能他在后面的桑拿房
Maybe he's back there in the sauna
当一条小"热狗"
like a little hotdog.
我的乖狗狗在哪儿
Where's my big boy?
说真的 我的乖狗狗在哪儿
Um, seriously, where's my big boy?
你不会刚才没关门吧
You didn't leave the door open, did you?
没有
No.
我敢保证他在屋里的某处
I'm sure he's in here somewhere.
布鲁诺 布鲁诺
Bruno? Bruno?
布鲁诺
Bruno?
正在寻找"布鲁诺"
Finding "Bruno."
麦克斯 真的很抱歉
Max, I'm really sorry.
或许我们用一只
Maybe we could replace the dog
外表一模一样的狗来代替它
with one that looks exactly the same.
就跟这里的男人换老婆一样
Like men here do with wives.
或者我们先别假设他死了
Or maybe we don't assume he's dead after six seconds
一起出去找他
and we go out there and find him.
好的 祝你好运
Okay, good luck.
你得跟我一起去
You are coming with me.
兰迪爱布鲁诺
Randy loves Bruno,
而我爱...喜欢兰迪
and I lo-uh-ike Randy.
别以为我没听见你差点说出口的那句话
Don't think I didn't hear what you almost said.
-我们得找到那只狗 -可天越来越黑了
- We need to find the dog. - But it's getting dark
外面还有人想要杀掉我们
and there's someone out there who wants to kill us.
相信我 里面也有人想要杀掉你
Trust me, there's someone in there who wants to kill you.
手电 我们需要手电
Flashlights. We need flashlights.
你爱...喜欢他
You lo-uh-ike him.
现在这里有两个人想杀掉你
Now there are two people in here who want to kill you.
快出来 乖狗狗
Come here, big boy.
天啊 他腿这么短怎么能跑这么远
God, how could he have gotten this far on such little legs?
我不知道 丹尼·德·维托貌似也爱到处跑
I don't know, Danny DeVito seems to get around a lot.
即使你告诉兰迪这全是你的错
Even when you tell Randy this is 100% your fault,
他还是会跟我分手
he is still gonna break up with me.
麦克斯 你才跟他在一起四天
Max, you've been with him four days.
我知道 这是我时间最长的恋爱
I know, it's my longest relationship.
真的很抱歉 麦克斯 我们会找到他的
I'm really sorry, Max. We'll find him.
老天
Oh, my God!
-你看见布鲁诺了吗 -不 我手机有信号了
- What, you see Bruno? - No, I see bars on my phone.
我们得待在这里别动
We have to stay right here.
我视频的时间快到了
It's almost time for my FaceTime.
把那该死的手机给我
Give me that stupid thing.
我要收进我的裤子里
I'll put it down my pants.
那我就伸手去掏
And I'll go get it.
你得专心
You gotta focus
帮我找到那条狗
and help me find that dog.
我不想搞砸和兰迪的关系 失去他
I don't want to ruin things with Randy
或失去他的房子
or his house.
麦克斯 这太过界了
Max, this is so far past boundaries.
别跟我说什么界限
Oh, don't talk to me about boundaries.
是谁把狗放出去的 谁
Who let the dog out? Who?
谁 谁 谁[有同词歌曲]
Who-who-who-who?
我大二那年也是这么对凯文·伯灵顿说
As I said to Kevin Burlington my sophomore year of college,
"接受事实吧"
"Just take it."
这事很严重
This is serious.
兰迪给了我很多
Randy has given me so much.
眼镜 礼品篮
Sunglasses, gift baskets,
四目相对的高潮
an orgasm with eye contact.
-我的老天 -我知道
- Oh, my God. - I know.
通常我都直接把男人的脸推开
Usually, I have to push their face away.
不 你看
No, look.
我们在好莱坞标牌的底端
We're at the foot of the Hollywood sign.
来张自拍啊
Quick selfie?
必须得拍啊 不是吗
I mean, we have to, right?
先找到狗 等回来的时候再拍
On the way back, once we find the dog.
这事我们一定得做
Which we are definitely going to do.
詹妮弗·劳伦斯打来了
Jennifer Lawrence is calling.
你居然挂了大表姐的电话
Did you just hang up on J Law?
我很确定这违反了"表"法
I'm pretty sure that's against the J Law.
你现在在外面 是因为你弄丢了兰迪的狗
You're out here because you lost Randy's dog,
那边还站了一个陌生男人
and there's a strange man standing over there,
而你满脑子却只有詹妮弗·劳伦斯
and all you can think about is Jennifer Lawrence.
你刚是说那边站了一个陌生男人吗
Did you just say there's a strange man standing over there?
天啊 是的
Oh, my God, I did.
瞧
Look...
是一个穿着脏兮兮运动服的老阿伯
See there, the old guy in the stained sweat suit.
他肯定是兰迪的邻居
Oh, he must be Randy's neighbor.
他在外面干什么
What's he doing out here?
你找到布鲁诺了
Oh, you found Bruno!
真有意思 刚才有一瞬间
It's so funny, for a second
我还以为他是吃人肉的杀人狂呢
I thought he was the cannibal murderer.
天啊 他手里拿着刀
Oh, my God, he has a knife.
或许他在拆包裹呢
Maybe he's just opening packages.
过来 快过来 乖狗狗
Come here. Come here, big boy.
-快跑 麦克斯 -过来 乖狗狗
- Uh...run, Max! - Come here, big boy.
-快 -这里没啥可吃
- Come on. - Nothing to eat here.
我肉硬又难嚼
I'm stringy and chewy.
快
Quick!
快 上去
Quick, up here!
或许直升飞机会看见我们
Maybe the helicopters will see us.
是啊 如果看不见
Yeah, and if not,
我们可以从"O"标牌跳下来自杀
we can throw ourselves off the O.
我拒绝被一个老头吃掉
I refuse to get eaten by an old man...
而且是连银行户头都没有的老头
without a bank account.
食人狂魔会爬上来吗
Can cannibals climb?
他们不是"爬梯狂魔" 所以应该没事
Well, they're not called "Climbables," So that's good.
他还在那里吗
Is he still there?
我们很快就会知道了
Well, we'll know in a second
因为在一个饥饿的食人族旁边大叫
'cause you're screaming within earshot
他听得到好吗
of a hungry people-eater.
你被包围了 把你的双手举起来
You are surrounded! Put your hands up!
麦克斯 警察来了
Max, the police are here.
我们安全了 安全了
We're safe. We're safe.
那是你而已
Speak for yourself.
严格说来 我应该在康州服在家软禁刑法
I'm technically under house arrest in Connecticut.
我让他吃冰淇淋
I let him eat ice cream.
这是他应得的
He deserves it.
谁昨天过得很不顺呀
Who had a rough day yesterday?
真的很抱歉 兰迪
I am really sorry, Randy.
你一定认为我是一个不负责任的人
You must think I'm as irresponsible as I am.
你该出场了 快哭着
This is where you cry
告诉他都是你的错 而我是一个完人
and tell him it's all you and I'm perfect.
抱歉 我刚在想
Sorry, I was just thinking,
那狗的牙齿和牙龈看起来比我的还健康
that dog's gums and teeth look healthier than mine.
我至今仍不敢相信我的邻居
I still can't believe my neighbor
居然是食人狂魔沃尔特·加里·万斯
was Walter Gary Vance the cannibal.
老实说 这比住在科特妮·洛芙隔壁还糟得多
And honestly, it was way worse living next to Courtney Love.
其实我要求也不高
I mean, it's not that hard.
蓝色垃圾箱是可回收物
Blue bins are for recycling,
每周二是街道清扫
Tuesdays are street cleaning,
不要在我门廊吸毒
Don't do heroin on my porch.
是啊 那是一项私家车道上的"运动"
Yeah, that's a driveway sport.
布鲁诺以前也曾跑出去过
Look, Bruno's gotten out before,
但你们特意跑出去找他
but the fact that you went out there to look for him
还冒着生命危险
and risked your lives.
你们真勇敢
I mean, you were fearless.
随便吧 或许有那么一点吧
Pfft, whatever. Maybe a little.
这下好了 詹妮弗·劳伦斯拜拜了
Ugh, great. Jennifer Lawrence just passed.
她死了吗
She's dead?
不 她跟我的电影拜拜了
No, she passed on the movie.
那是她的损失
It's her loss.
好吧 是你的损失 但我觉得欠你人情
Well, it's your loss, but I feel like I owe you
毕竟你冒着生命危险去找我男朋友的狗
for risking your life to find my boyfriend's dog.
不是说你是我的男朋友啊
Not that you're my boyfriend,
因为超恶心
'cause gross.
能当你的男朋友 真是三生有幸
I'd be lucky to be your boyfriend.
提前是我是 但幸好我不是
If I was, which yuck, I'm not.
大家安安
Hey, everybody.
瞧瞧 我的精神已经升华了
Look, I'm spiritually evolved now.
是啊 冥想让我的膝盖难受
Yeah, you know, the meditating was screwing up my knees,
所以我从公车站的一个印度女人那买了这装束
so I bought this getup from an Indian woman at a bus stop.
印度跟冥想差不多 这样轻松多了
Yeah, it's a lot easier.
苏菲 这束花真美
Sophie, those flowers are beautiful.
是啊
Yeah...
这是送你的
and they're for you.
这束花会对我做什么吗
What're they gonna do to me?
它们代表的是爱意和善意之举
They're an act of love and kindness.
苏菲 这真是你对我说过最好听的话了
Sophie, that's literally the nicest thing you've ever said to me.
是啊
Oh, yeah.
我不知道是不是因为我灵气变干净了
I don't know if it's my aura's clean,
还是这颗价值12.95元的眉心痣作祟
or it's the 12.95 Bindi dot I'm wearing,
但我是真的发自内心的
but I really do mean it.
苏菲 别吃 那是狗吃的冰淇淋
Oh, Sophie, no. That's dog ice cream.
少多管闲事 婊砸
Mind your own business, bitch!
一秒钟破功
And we're back.